15,000 followers, 90 days,
and if not, back to the nine to five.
Here's how we're gonna do it.
If you're also trying to be the next eight girl
and you wanna grow on your platforms,
you're in the right spot.
Number one, and I know everybody's tired of hearing this,
but consistency really is key.
But we're focusing on quantity without risking the quality.
I want y'all to be so fucking tired of seeing my face.
I want you to see me on your feet and think damn again,
you need to get people so used to seeing your face
to the point where they're thinking,
"Oh, I wonder what Tori is doing next."
And grain yourself in their brain
so that they cannot forget.
Baby, I live in your hippocampus now.
What's the hippocampus?
- The hippocampus is a part of the brain
that is primarily associated with memory.
- There you go.
Number two, SEO.
If you don't know, it stands for search engine optimization.
What's the point of good content?
If nobody can find it.
Number three, authenticity and transparency.
Zero (beep)
I'm showing y'all the successes, the failures,
exactly what works and what doesn't work for me
so that you guys can apply this to your growth strategy.
I'll be updating you guys every week
on exactly what's working, what I'm trying,
what needs to be fixed and what I'm learning along the way
so that you guys can go and apply this to your content.
And with that, I'll see you in the next video.
Go be great and I'll catch you on the flip.